const qBank = [
  {
    question:
      "You need to think ahead before taking such important decisions",
    answers: ["think ahead", "think before", "think after", "think"],
    correct: "think ahead",
    questionId: "000000"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Thinking ahead I don't  think that's really worth it",
    answers: ["Thinking ahead", "Thinking", "Thinking before", "Thinking after"],
    correct: "Thinking ahead",
    questionId: "000001"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I some serious obstacles",
    answers: ["came up against", "came up", "came up to", "came up opposite"],
    correct: "came up against",
    questionId: "000002"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I some serious obstacles while doing it",
    answers: ["came up against", "came up", "came up opposite", "came up to"],
    correct: "came up against",
    questionId: "001003"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I some serious difficulties while trying to do it ",
    answers: ["came up against", "came up", "came up opposite", "came up to"],
    correct: "came up against",
    questionId: "001004"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He's to shy to ask her out",
    answers: ["ask her out", "ask ", "ask for", "ask about"],
    correct: "ask her out",
    questionId: "001005"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Why don't you ask her out?",
    answers: ["ask her out", "ask ", "ask for", "ask about"],
    correct: "ask her put",
    questionId: "001006"
  },
  {
    question:
        "i'll try to get my message across",
    answers: ["get my message across", "get ", "get about", "get for"],
    correct: "get my message across",
    questionId: "001007"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll try to get my idea across",
    answers: ["get my idea across", "get ", "get about", "get for"],
    correct: "get my idea across",
    questionId: "001008"
  },
  {
    question:
        "i noted down her phone number ",
    answers: ["noted down", "noted", "noted to", "noted about"],
    correct: "noted down",
    questionId: "001009"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You'd better noted it down",
    answers: ["noted down", "noted", "noted to", "noted about"],
    correct: "noted down",
    questionId: "001010"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If i were you, I wouldn't dwell on these problems",
    answers: ["dwell on", "dwell", "dwell after", "dwell for"],
    correct: "dwell on",
    questionId: "001011"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As you see, some mistakes were made, but there is no need to dwell on it too much",
    answers: ["dwell on", "dwell", "dwell after", "dwell for"],
    correct: "dwell on",
    questionId: "001012"
  },
  {
    question:
        "All goods were bought up",
    answers: ["bought up", "bought", "bought in", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Thinking ahead",
    questionId: "001013"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They bought up all the land in that area",
    answers: ["bought up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "bought up",
    questionId: "001014"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I won't be surprised if the price goes up",
    answers: ["goes up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "goes up",
    questionId: "001015"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The price went up by twenty percent",
    answers: ["went up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "went up",
    questionId: "001016"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I haven't back up these files yet it's in my plans",
    answers: ["back up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "back up",
    questionId: "001017"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You'd better back up all these files just in case",
    answers: ["back up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "back up",
    questionId: "001018"
  },
  {
    question:
        "When will you be able to meet up",
    answers: ["meet up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "meet up",
    questionId: "001019"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I suppose that we could meet up the day after tomorrow",
    answers: ["meet up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "meet up",
    questionId: "001020"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He turned into  a very successful businessman",
    answers: ["turned into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turned into",
    questionId: "001021"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It turned into a real nightmare",
    answers: ["turned into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turned into",
    questionId: "001022"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It calls for more efforts",
    answers: ["calls for", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "calls for",
    questionId: "001023"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It really strikes me that here is still so much uncertainty concerning this issue",
    answers: ["uncertainty concerning", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "uncertainty concerning",
    questionId: "001024"
  },
  {
    question:
        "On the one hand, I'd really like to enrol in this course",
    answers: ["On the one hand", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "On the one hand",
    questionId: "001025"
  },
  {
    question:
        "On the hand, i'm not quit sure that it's really something worthwhile",
    answers: ["quit sure", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "quit sure",
    questionId: "001026"
  },
  {
    question:
        "On the one hand, I'd really like to enrol in this course",
    answers: ["really like", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "really like",
    questionId: "001027"
  },
  {
    question:
        "On the one hand, I'm not entirely sure that it's really worth doing",
    answers: ["entirely sure", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "entirely sure",
    questionId: "001028"
  },
  {
    question:
        "On the one hand, I can earn a plenty of money there but, on teh other hand, it doesn't seem so attractive in the long run ",
    answers: ["earn a plenty of money", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "earn a plenty of money",
    questionId: "001029"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I totally share your point of view",
    answers: ["totally share your point", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "totally share your point",
    questionId: "001030"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I fully agree with you",
    answers: ["fully agree", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "fully agree",
    questionId: "001031"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I can't figure out what the best solution to such a complicated issue is",
    answers: ["figure out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "figure out",
    questionId: "001032"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I can't figure out what the best course of action is in this case",
    answers: ["figure out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "figure out",
    questionId: "001033"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I came up with one brilliant idea",
    answers: ["came up with", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "came up with",
    questionId: "001034"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Looking back, i came to the conclusion that it was a very meaningful event",
    answers: ["Looking back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Looking back",
    questionId: "001035"
  },
  {
    question:
        "No doubt, he made a very meaningful contribution to our society",
    answers: ["No doubt", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "No doubt",
    questionId: "001035"
  },
  {
    question:
        "No doubt, he's made a very meaningful contribution to our society and, surprisingly enough, he isn't going to stop",
    answers: ["No doubt", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "No doubt",
    questionId: "001037"
  },
  {
    question:
        "What I mean is that it's supposedly the best decision in such situation",
    answers: ["What I mean", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "What I mean",
    questionId: "001038"
  },
  {
    question:
        "What I mean is that it's supposedly the best course of action in this case",
    answers: ["What I mean", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "What I mean",
    questionId: "001039"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Whht i'm trying to say is that we can't ignore this seemingly unimportant detail",
    answers: ["What i'm trying to say", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "What i'm trying to say",
    questionId: "001040"
  },
  {
    question:
        "What i'm trying to say is that we need to be much more persistent if we really want to achieve a certain aim",
    answers: ["What i'm trying to say", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "What i'm trying to say",
    questionId: "001041"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as, i'm concerned I've never been interested in it",
    answers: ["As far as, I'm concerned", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "As far as, I'm concerned",
    questionId: "001042"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as, I'm concerned, I've never paid attention to it ",
    answers: ["As far as, I'm concerned", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "As far as, I'm concerned",
    questionId: "001042"
  },,
  {
    question:
        "As far as, I'm concerned, I've always paid attention to it ",
    answers: ["As far as, I'm concerned", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "As far as, I'm concerned",
    questionId: "001044"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as my previous job is concerned it was a very valuable experience",
    answers: ["As far as my previous job is concerned", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "As far as my previous job is concerned",
    questionId: "001044"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as this job is concerned, I'm absolutely sure that it's  a very valuable experience",
    answers: ["As far as this job is concerned", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "As far as this job is concerned",
    questionId: "001045"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as my friends are concerned, they're always ready to support me and I really value it",
    answers: ["As far as ", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "As far as ",
    questionId: "001046"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as this video is concerned, it's extremely useful for educational purpose",
    answers: ["As far as ", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "As far as ",
    questionId: "001047"
  },
  {
    question:
        "i'm not quit sure about it",
    answers: ["quit sure", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "quit sure",
    questionId: "001048"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'm not entirely sure about it",
    answers: ["entirely sure", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "entirely sure",
    questionId: "001049"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'm not quit sure that the game is worth the candle",
    answers: ["worth the candle", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "worth the candle",
    questionId: "001050"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I tend to think that we shouldn't disregard quality in search of a lower price",
    answers: ["I tend to think", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "I tend to think",
    questionId: "001051"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As it seems to me, the game is not worth the candle ",
    answers: ["As it seems to me", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "As it seems to me",
    questionId: "001052"
  },
  {
    question:
        "what seems to me is that they behave totally irresponsibly",
    answers: ["what seems to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "what seems to",
    questionId: "001053"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I have to say that I've always been interested in learning foreign languages",
    answers: ["interested in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "interested in",
    questionId: "001054"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I have to say that I've always been particularly interested in it ",
    answers: ["interested in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "interested in",
    questionId: "001055"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I have to add that I've always been keen on music ",
    answers: ["keen on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "keen on",
    questionId: "001056"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I have to add that I've always been keen on music",
    answers: ["keen on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "keen on",
    questionId: "001057"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'd like to point out that unfortunately we can't influence ",
    answers: ["point out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "point out",
    questionId: "001058"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'd like to point out that it had a great influence on me when I was a child",
    answers: ["point out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "point out",
    questionId: "001059"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It really strikes me that they haven't solved this problem yet",
    answers: ["strikes", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "strikes",
    questionId: "001060"
  },
  {
    question:
        "What really strikes me about all this that they don't " +
        "really understand what's really going on at present",
    answers: ["going on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "going on",
    questionId: "001061"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It really strikes me that there is still so much uncertainty concerning this issue",
    answers: ["uncertainty concerning", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "uncertainty concerning",
    questionId: "001062"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'm afraid that we're running out od time so we need to hurry up",
    answers: ["running out of", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "running out of",
    questionId: "001063"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as I can see we've run out of time ",
    answers: ["run out of", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "run out of",
    questionId: "001064"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Let's get down to work",
    answers: ["get down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get down",
    questionId: "001065"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It's time to get down to learning english",
    answers: ["get down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get down",
    questionId: "001066"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'd like to point out that this issue is of great importance and it shouldn't be ignored",
    answers: ["point out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "point out",
    questionId: "001067"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'd like to point out how important it is",
    answers: ["point out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "point out",
    questionId: "001068"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It goes without saying that she'd like to " +
        "go on learning english here unless he riches the next level ",
    answers: ["go on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "go on",
    questionId: "001069"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I can't understand what's going on here ",
    answers: ["going on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "going on",
    questionId: "001070"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I can't figure out what's going on",
    answers: ["figure out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "figure out",
    questionId: "001071"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I can't figure out how it can be done better",
    answers: ["figure out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "figure out",
    questionId: "001072"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I try not ot give up whatever happens",
    answers: ["give up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "give up",
    questionId: "001073"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I stick to the point that we shouldn't give up whatever difficulties we face ",
    answers: ["give up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "give up",
    questionId: "001074"
  },
  {
    question:
        "To tell the truth, I can't figure out how this problem can be sorted out",
    answers: ["sorted out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sorted out",
    questionId: "001075"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If I were you, I would try to sort out the following problems as soon as possible",
    answers: ["sort out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sort out",
    questionId: "001076"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As they say, never put off till tomorrow what you can do today",
    answers: ["put off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put off",
    questionId: "001077"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As it's said, never put off till tomorrow what can be done today ",
    answers: ["put off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put off",
    questionId: "001078"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As they said, the trip may be called off ",
    answers: ["called off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "called off",
    questionId: "001079"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As they say, the trip might be called off",
    answers: ["called off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "called off",
    questionId: "001080"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As you might guess, I can't do without it",
    answers: ["do without", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "do without",
    questionId: "001081"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It's not exaggeration to say that, I don't really know what I would do without you",
    answers: ["do without", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "do without",
    questionId: "001082"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I need some time to think it over before making a final decision",
    answers: ["Think over", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Think over",
    questionId: "001083"
  },
  {
    question:
        "To tell the truth, i'd like to think it over first",
    answers: ["Think over", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Think over",
    questionId: "001084"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Hold on a second",
    answers: ["hold on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "hold on",
    questionId: "001085"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Hold on a minute",
    answers: ["hold on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "hold on",
    questionId: "001086"
  },
  {
    question:
        "When i found out the whole truth, i was totaly shoked",
    answers: ["find out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "find out",
    questionId: "001087"
  },
  {
    question:
        "To find out more, you can visit our website",
    answers: ["find out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "find out",
    questionId: "001088"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I get on with my neighbors pretty well",
    answers: ["get on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get on",
    questionId: "001089"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I get on with my colleagues pretty well",
    answers: ["get on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get on",
    questionId: "001090"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As you might guess, i'm not going to put up with this injustice ",
    answers: ["put up with", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put up with",
    questionId: "001091"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I have to say that I can't put up with it anymore",
    answers: ["put up with", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put up with",
    questionId: "001092"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'm currently looking for new opportunities for further development",
    answers: ["looking for", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "looking for",
    questionId: "001093"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'm currently looking for a more well-paid job",
    answers: ["looking for", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "looking for",
    questionId: "001094"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If I were you, I would throw it away at once",
    answers: ["throw it away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "throw it away",
    questionId: "001095"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I don't throw it away because it can come in handy",
    answers: ["throw it away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "throw it away",
    questionId: "001096"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I realize that I'll have to do it over",
    answers: ["Thinking ahead", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Thinking ahead",
    questionId: "001097"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I realized that I would have to do it over",
    answers: ["do over", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "do over",
    questionId: "001098"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I can't keep up with you/ Van you wait a bit?",
    answers: ["keep up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "keep up",
    questionId: "001099"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Can you wait a little? I can't keep up",
    answers: ["keep up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "keep up",
    questionId: "001100"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I missed a several lessons and it ttok me a while to catch up with the rest",
    answers: ["catch up with", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "catch up with",
    questionId: "001101"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I know that my level is quit low at present but I'll try to catch up with the rest.",
    answers: ["catch up with", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "catch up with",
    questionId: "001102"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Metals with the excessive stress for them can break down, melt.",
    answers: ["break down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "break down",
    questionId: "001103"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She said that she would look after the kids",
    answers: ["look after", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look after",
    questionId: "001104"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She's been looking after the kids all day.",
    answers: ["looking after", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "looking after",
    questionId: "001105"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If you don't hurry up, you can fall behind.",
    answers: ["fall behind", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "fall behind",
    questionId: "001106"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'm going to double my efforts because I don't want to fall behind",
    answers: ["fall behind", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "fall behind",
    questionId: "001107"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You need to calm down a bit!",
    answers: ["calm down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "calm down",
    questionId: "001108"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Calm down! There is no need to worry",
    answers: ["Calm down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Calm down",
    questionId: "001109"
  },
  {
    question:
        "What about eating out tonight?",
    answers: ["eating out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "eating out",
    questionId: "001110"
  },
  {
    question:
        "How about eating out to night?",
    answers: ["eating out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "eating out",
    questionId: "001111"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I have to say that I really hate getting up so early",
    answers: ["getting up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "getting up",
    questionId: "001112"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I used to get up very early when i worked there",
    answers: ["get up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get up",
    questionId: "001113"
  },
  {
    question:
        "By the time he called me, I had already woken up",
    answers: ["woken up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "woken up",
    questionId: "001114"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that he would wake me up when it was time to leave",
    answers: ["wake up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "wake up",
    questionId: '001115'
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as i know, he works out in teh gym several times a week",
    answers: ["works out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "works out",
    questionId: "001116"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Have you ever thought about working out in the gym?",
    answers: ["working out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "working out",
    questionId: "001117"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I was asked to feel in the form",
    answers: ["feel in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "feel in",
    questionId: "001118"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We were asked to feel in the form and indicate all necessary information",
    answers: ["feel in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "feel in",
    questionId: "001119"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I haven't turn on the computer yet",
    answers: ["switch on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "switch on",
    questionId: "001120"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Is the computer turn on?",
    answers: ["switch on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "switch on",
    questionId: "001121"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Could you switch on the light, please",
    answers: ["switch on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "switch on",
    questionId: "001122"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I need to switch on the light because it's getting really dark",
    answers: ["Thinking ahead", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Thinking ahead",
    questionId: "001123"
  },
  {
    question:
        "When I left home, I realized that I had forgotten to turn off the light",
    answers: ["turn off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turn off",
    questionId: "001124"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Don't forget tu turn off the light before leaving",
    answers: ["turn off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turn off",
    questionId: "001125"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I've already switched off the computer",
    answers: ["switched off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "switched off",
    questionId: "001126"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I haven't been able to get in touch with her " +
        "for the last few hours because her phone is switched off",
    answers: ["get in touch with", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get in touch with",
    questionId: "001127"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Can you turn up  the volume a bit?",
    answers: ["turn up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turn up",
    questionId: "001128"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Can you turn up  the volume a little?",
    answers: ["turn up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turn up",
    questionId: "001129"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The music was so loud that I turned it down",
    answers: ["turn down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turn down",
    questionId: "001130"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Can you turn down the music",
    answers: ["turn down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turn down",
    questionId: "001131"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said the he would never come back there",
    answers: ["came back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "came back",
    questionId: "001132"
  },
  {
    question:
        "By the time jhe came back, I had already finished doing that exercise",
    answers: ["came back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "came back",
    questionId: "001133"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Let's get back to our conversation",
    answers: ["get back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get back",
    questionId: "001134"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We've been talking for so long! I think it's time to get back to work",
    answers: ["get back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get back",
    questionId: "001135"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll call you back as soon as I get free",
    answers: ["call back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "call back",
    questionId: "001136"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I told her that I would call her back as soon as I got free",
    answers: ["call back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "call back",
    questionId: "001137"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He stayed at home because his car had broken down",
    answers: ["broken down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "broken down",
    questionId: "001138"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Not surprisingly, his often broken down because it was really old",
    answers: ["broken down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "broken down",
    questionId: "001139"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Who brought him up",
    answers: ["brought up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "brought up",
    questionId: "001140"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Who was he brought up by",
    answers: ["brought up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "brought up",
    questionId: "001141"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Despite  he grew up in a very poor family, he got an excellent education and became a real expert in this area ",
    answers: ["grew up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "grew up",
    questionId: "001142"
  },
  {
    question:
        "In spite of the fact that he grew up in disadvantage family, he managed to succeed in life",
    answers: ["grew up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "grew up",
    questionId: "001143"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll certainly carry on doing it!",
    answers: ["carry on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "carry on",
    questionId: "001144"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Let's carry on our discussion",
    answers: ["carry on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "carry on",
    questionId: "001145"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Cheer up ! The news isn't as bad as it seems",
    answers: ["Cheer up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Cheer up",
    questionId: "001146"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Cheer up ! Th news isn't as bad as may seem",
    answers: ["Cheer up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Cheer up",
    questionId: "001147"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I've never come across this expression before. It's completely new for me",
    answers: ["came across", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "came across",
    questionId: "001148"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I came across so many new words while reading this article",
    answers: ["came across", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "came across",
    questionId: "001149"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You know, I came up with a very unusual idea",
    answers: ["came up with", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "came up with",
    questionId: "001150"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Listen! I came up with an absolutely brilliant idea",
    answers: ["came up with", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "came up with",
    questionId: "001151"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You need to do up the seat belt",
    answers: ["do up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "do up",
    questionId: "001152"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Do up the coat or you can get cold!",
    answers: ["do up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "do up",
    questionId: "001153"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The tree has cut down this week",
    answers: ["cut down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "cut down",
    questionId: "001154"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that someone had cut down the tree",
    answers: ["cut down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "cut down",
    questionId: "001155"
  },
  {
    question:
        "he cut down on chocolate to keep a more balanced diet",
    answers: ["cut down on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "cut down on",
    questionId: "001156"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She was advised to cut down on chocolate to lose waight",
    answers: ["cut down on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "cut down on",
    questionId: "001157"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We got on the train",
    answers: ["got on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "got on",
    questionId: "001158"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I got on the bus",
    answers: ["got on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "got on",
    questionId: "001159"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We got off the train",
    answers: ["got off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "got off",
    questionId: "001160"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I got into the taxi",
    answers: ["get into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get into",
    questionId: "001161"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The lock broke down and we weren't able to get into the house",
    answers: ["get into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get into",
    questionId: "001162"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Luckily, I managed to get into this university",
    answers: ["get into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get into",
    questionId: "001163"
  },
  {
    question:
        "we need to hurry up or we won't be able to catch up with them",
    answers: ["hurry up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "hurry up",
    questionId: "001164"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We need to hurry up or we won't to be able to keep up with them",
    answers: ["hurry up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "hurry up",
    questionId: "001165"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I look forward to hearing from you soon",
    answers: ["look forward", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look forward",
    questionId: "001166"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I look forward to your reply",
    answers: ["look forward", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look forward",
    questionId: "001167"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The police are looking into this crime",
    answers: ["looking into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "looking into",
    questionId: "001168"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He says that they'll look into this matter",
    answers: ["look into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look into",
    questionId: "001169"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If you don't know the meaning of this word, look it up in a dictionary",
    answers: ["look it up in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look it up in",
    questionId: "001170"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You'd better look it up in a dictionary",
    answers: ["look it up in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look it up in",
    questionId: "001171"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He picked up the note, which was lying on the ground, and read it",
    answers: ["picked up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "picked up",
    questionId: "001172"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that he would pick up you after work",
    answers: ["pick up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "pick up",
    questionId: "001173"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Unfortunately, he couldn't pay back all the money",
    answers: ["pay back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "pay back",
    questionId: "001174"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He promised that he would pay back all the money",
    answers: ["pay back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "pay back",
    questionId: "001175"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She was so angry that she hung up the phone",
    answers: ["hang up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "hang up",
    questionId: "001176"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She was forced to hang up the phone",
    answers: ["hang up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "hang up",
    questionId: "001177"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He turned out to be right",
    answers: ["turned out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turned out",
    questionId: "001178"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As it turned out, that accusation was absolutely groundless ",
    answers: ["turned out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turned out",
    questionId: "001179"
  },
  {
    question:
        "This news brighten up my day",
    answers: ["brighten up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "brighten up",
    questionId: "001180"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Definitely, it'll brighten up your life",
    answers: ["brighten up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "brighten up",
    questionId: "001181"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He finally paid off the loan",
    answers: ["pay off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "pay off",
    questionId: "001182"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He decided not to take a loan because he was really afraid that he would't be able to pay it off",
    answers: ["pay off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "pay off",
    questionId: "001183"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'm sure that your hard work will pay off in the end",
    answers: ["pay off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "pay off",
    questionId: "001184"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You need to keep in mind that this plan can also fall apart",
    answers: ["fall apart", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "fall apart",
    questionId: "001185"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It isn't surprising that his bike falling apart. It's so old",
    answers: ["falling apart", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "falling apart",
    questionId: "001186"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He set up a very profitable, thriving company and became a millionaire",
    answers: ["set up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "set up",
    questionId: "001187"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that he hadn't set up this program yet",
    answers: ["set up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "set up",
    questionId: "001188"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We were told to make up oor own sentences",
    answers: ["make up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "make up",
    questionId: "001189"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You know, I made up my mind to do it on my own",
    answers: ["made up my mind to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "made up my mind to",
    questionId: "001190"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He stood up to ask the question",
    answers: ["stood up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "stood up",
    questionId: "001191"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She closed the book and stood up",
    answers: ["stood up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "stood up",
    questionId: "001192"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He was twenty when the war broke out ",
    answers: ["broke out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "broke out",
    questionId: "001193"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They were in the yard when the fire broke out",
    answers: ["broke out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "broke out",
    questionId: "001194"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It took him about a year to save up for a new car",
    answers: ["save up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "save up",
    questionId: "001195"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He's currently trying to save up for holiday",
    answers: ["save up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "save up",
    questionId: "001196"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Don't forget to put out the fire before leaving",
    answers: ["put out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put out",
    questionId: "001197"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The fire was so intense that it took them about five hours to put out it",
    answers: ["put out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put out",
    questionId: "001198"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The game ended in a draw",
    answers: ["ended in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "ended in",
    questionId: "001199"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Time goes by so quickly",
    answers: ["goes by", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "goes by",
    questionId: "001200"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We all see that time goes by so fast",
    answers: ["goes by", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "goes by",
    questionId: "001201"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The more i live the more i understand that time goes by so quickly",
    answers: ["goes by", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "goes by",
    questionId: "001202"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Watch out! It can fall off",
    answers: ["Watch out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Watch out",
    questionId: "001203"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as I can judge, this job doesn't measure up to his expectations",
    answers: ["measure up to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "measure up to",
    questionId: "001204"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The quality of this product doesn't measure up to certain requirements",
    answers: ["measure up to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "measure up to",
    questionId: "001205"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The kids grew out of these clothes",
    answers: ["grew out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "grew out",
    questionId: "001206"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She said that he had grown out of those clothes",
    answers: ["grown out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "grown out",
    questionId: "001207"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll see you off",
    answers: ["see off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "see off",
    questionId: "001208"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll see off you if you don't mind",
    answers: ["see off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "see off",
    questionId: "001209"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I didn't like this idea in the beginning but than it grew on me ",
    answers: ["grew on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "grew on",
    questionId: "001210"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I didn't like this format of education but than it grew on me ",
    answers: ["grew on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "grew on",
    questionId: "001211"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It was decided to close down the factory",
    answers: ["close down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "close down",
    questionId: "001212"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It was reported that the popular chain of supermarkets would have to close down for good",
    answers: ["close down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "close down",
    questionId: "001213"
  },
  {
    question:
        "How do you usually get to work? By car, by bus or on foot",
    answers: ["get to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get to",
    questionId: "001214"
  },
  {
    question:
        "How long does it take you to get to work",
    answers: ["get to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get to",
    questionId: "001215"
  },
  {
    question:
        "What's the best way to get to this place?",
    answers: ["get to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get to",
    questionId: "001216"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Th only way to get to this place on foot",
    answers: ["on foot", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "on foot",
    questionId: "001217"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll take care of it while he's away",
    answers: ["is away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "is away",
    questionId: "001218"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that he would take care of it while she's away",
    answers: ["is away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "is away",
    questionId: "001219"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They started  climbing down the mountain because it was getting really dark",
    answers: ["climbing down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "climbing down",
    questionId: "001220"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He climbed up the tree and then climbed it down",
    answers: ["climbed up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "climbed up",
    questionId: "001221"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Let's talk it over",
    answers: ["talk it over", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "talk it over",
    questionId: "001222"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'd like to talk it over with you",
    answers: ["talk it over", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "talk it over",
    questionId: "001223"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You need to sign in",
    answers: ["sign in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sign in",
    questionId: "001224"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Use your account to sign in",
    answers: ["account to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "account to",
    questionId: "001225"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Yoy need to sign out of your account",
    answers: ["sign out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sign out",
    questionId: "001226"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Don't forget to sign out of your account!",
    answers: ["sign out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sign out",
    questionId: "001227"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He needs to give back this money",
    answers: ["give back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "give back",
    questionId: "001228"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She said that she needed to give back that money to him",
    answers: ["give back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "give back",
    questionId: "001229"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The plane will take off in a minute",
    answers: ["take off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "take off",
    questionId: "001230"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It was announced that the plane would take off in a hour",
    answers: ["take off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "take off",
    questionId: "001231"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Unfortunately, the party didn't live up my expectations ",
    answers: ["live up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "live up",
    questionId: "001232"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Unfortunately, this event didn't live up my expectations at all",
    answers: ["live up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "live up",
    questionId: "001233"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Keep it up!",
    answers: ["Keep up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Keep up",
    questionId: "001234"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Keep up the good work!",
    answers: ["Keep up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Keep up",
    questionId: "001235"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Who will make up for these losses",
    answers: ["make up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "make up",
    questionId: "001236"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I made up my mind to train much more intensively because I really wanted to make up for lost time",
    answers: ["made up my mind/make up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "made up my mind/make up",
    questionId: "001237"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They put forward several suggestions",
    answers: ["put forward", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put forward",
    questionId: "001238"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Various proposals were put forward during the meeting",
    answers: ["put forward", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put forward",
    questionId: "001239"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Come on/ let's go!",
    answers: ["Come on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Come on",
    questionId: "001240"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Come on' let's hurry up!",
    answers: ["hurry up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "hurry up",
    questionId: "001241"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She was so tired that she made up her mind to lie down",
    answers: ["lie down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "lie down",
    questionId: "001242"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'd like to lie down for a while",
    answers: ["lie down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "lie down",
    questionId: "001243"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'm really into it",
    answers: ["I'm really into'", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "I'm really into'",
    questionId: "001244"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I have to say i'm really into it",
    answers: ["'m into'", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "'m into'",
    questionId: "001245"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They broke into the house and stole the hidden money",
    answers: ["broke into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "broke into",
    questionId: "001246"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The police reported that someone had broken into their house",
    answers: ["broken into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "broken into",
    questionId: "001247"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I just want to sit down and relax",
    answers: ["sit down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sit down",
    questionId: "001248"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She said that she just wanted to sit down and relax",
    answers: ["sit down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sit down",
    questionId: "001249"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You'd better to write it down otherwise you'll forget it very easily",
    answers: ["write down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "write down",
    questionId: "001250"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll write it down just in case. I can't rely on my memory because it often lets me down",
    answers: ["let down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "let down",
    questionId: "001251"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that he had dropped out of college",
    answers: ["drop out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "drop out",
    questionId: "001252"
  },
  {
    question:
        "No one really expected that he would drop out the college",
    answers: ["drop out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "drop out",
    questionId: "001253"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They told me to hold the line and that they would put me through the sales department",
    answers: ["put me through", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put me through",
    questionId: "001254"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Please, hold the line. I'll put you through in a minute",
    answers: ["put through", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put through",
    questionId: "001255"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I was asked to put down my name and address",
    answers: ["put down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put down",
    questionId: "001256"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They need to stop putting him down",
    answers: ["putting him down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "putting him down",
    questionId: "001257"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He finally give in to their demands",
    answers: ["give in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "give in",
    questionId: "001258"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The government refused to give in their demands",
    answers: ["give in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "give in",
    questionId: "001259"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Let's move on to the next slide!",
    answers: ["move on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "move on",
    questionId: "001260"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Let's move on to the next point!",
    answers: ["move on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "move on",
    questionId: "001261"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They said that they already used up all the money",
    answers: ["used up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "used up",
    questionId: "001262"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It was said that all the money had already been used up",
    answers: ["used up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "used up",
    questionId: "001263"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'm going to sign up for this course",
    answers: ["sign up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sign up",
    questionId: "001264"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You can sign up this course in advance/beforehand",
    answers: ["sign up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sign up",
    questionId: "001265"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I feel that I need to focus on my studies",
    answers: ["focus on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "focus on",
    questionId: "001266"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He's planing to focus more on his carrier",
    answers: ["focus on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "focus on",
    questionId: "001267"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He asked me how long I would be away",
    answers: ["be away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "be away",
    questionId: "001268"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I had no idea how long i would be away",
    answers: ["be away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "be away",
    questionId: "001269"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You know, you can always count on my support",
    answers: ["count on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "count on",
    questionId: "001270"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If i were you, I wouldn't count on it",
    answers: ["count on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "count on",
    questionId: "001271"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It's really getting him down that there is still so much uncertainty",
    answers: ["getting him down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "getting him down",
    questionId: "001272"
  },
  {
    question:
        "This thought really gets him down",
    answers: ["gets him down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "gets him down",
    questionId: "001273"
  },
  {
    question:
        "These photos bring back very happy memories",
    answers: ["bring back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "bring back",
    questionId: "001274"
  },
  {
    question:
        "These photos bring back lots of happy reminiscences",
    answers: ["bring back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "bring back",
    questionId: "001275"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The electricity supply was cut off because of the storm",
    answers: ["cut off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "cut off",
    questionId: "001276"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He was completely cut off from outside world",
    answers: ["cut off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "cut off",
    questionId: "001277"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He just wanted to run away and hide",
    answers: ["run away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "run away",
    questionId: "001278"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Running away from your responsibilities and duties isn't the best idea because " +
        "it it won't solve this issue",
    answers: ["Running away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Running away",
    questionId: "001279"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Reading is a really come in handy a passtime",
    answers: ["come in handy", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "come in handy",
    questionId: "001280"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll stay in for a while",
    answers: ["stay in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "stay in",
    questionId: "001281"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I was so tired that i decided to stay in",
    answers: ["stay in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "stay in",
    questionId: "001282"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Could you speak up a bit",
    answers: ["speak up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "speak up",
    questionId: "001283"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Could you speak up a little",
    answers: ["speak up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "speak up",
    questionId: "001284"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He's easy to deal with",
    answers: ["deal with", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "deal with",
    questionId: "001285"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that he has fallen down and hurt his leg",
    answers: ["fallen down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "fallen down",
    questionId: "001286"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She slipped and fell down  the stairs",
    answers: ["fell down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "fell down",
    questionId: "001287"
  },
  {
    question:
        "To sum it didn't live up to my expectations at all",
    answers: ["sum up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sum up",
    questionId: "001288"
  },
  {
    question:
        "To sum up, there are certain advantages and disadvantages  of living here ",
    answers: ["sum up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sum up",
    questionId: "001289"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I often mix up this words",
    answers: ["mix up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "mix up",
    questionId: "001290"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Students often mix up these expressions",
    answers: ["mix up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "mix up",
    questionId: "001291"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The food can go off",
    answers: ["go off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "go off",
    questionId: "001292"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If you live the food here, it can go off",
    answers: ["go off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "go off",
    questionId: "001293"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The couple broke up two years ago",
    answers: ["broke up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "broke up",
    questionId: "001294"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that they had broken up so unexpectedly",
    answers: ["broken up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "broken up",
    questionId: "001295"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Go ahead ! We're all ears",
    answers: ["Go ahead", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Go ahead",
    questionId: "001295"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Go ahead ! I'm all ears",
    answers: ["Go ahead", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Go ahead",
    questionId: "001296"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It's virtually impossible to get by this money",
    answers: ["get by", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get by",
    questionId: "001297"
  },
  {
    question:
        "How can he get by on such a small salary",
    answers: ["get by on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get by on",
    questionId: "001298"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It was reported that he had been beaten up very badly",
    answers: ["beaten up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "beaten up",
    questionId: "001299"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Where do you come from originally?",
    answers: ["come from", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "come from",
    questionId: "001300"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Where does this quote come from?",
    answers: ["come from", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "come from",
    questionId: "001301"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as I can judge, he was ripped off in this store",
    answers: ["ripped off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "ripped off",
    questionId: "001302"
  },
  {
    question:
        "500 dollars for a pair of trousers! What a rip-off",
    answers: ["rip-off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "rip-off",
    questionId: "001303"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as know, they fall out only occasionally",
    answers: ["fall out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "fall out",
    questionId: "001304"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I have to say that they used to fell out a lot",
    answers: ["fell out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "fell out",
    questionId: "001305"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Have you ever thought about starting up your own company",
    answers: ["starting up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "starting up",
    questionId: "001306"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Frankly speaking, I've never thought about starting up my own firm",
    answers: ["starting up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "starting up",
    questionId: "001307"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If I were you, I would try to weigh up all advantages and disadvantages of this offer",
    answers: ["weigh up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "weigh up",
    questionId: "001308"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'd like to weigh up all pros and cons",
    answers: ["weigh up all pros and cons", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "weigh up all pros and cons",
    questionId: "001309"
  },
  {
    question:
        "This document hasn't printed out yet",
    answers: ["printed out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "printed out",
    questionId: "001310"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I printed out what I had typed",
    answers: ["printed out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "printed out",
    questionId: "001311"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You know, I was held up in traffic jem",
    answers: ["held up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "held up",
    questionId: "001312"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that their flight had been held up",
    answers: ["held up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "held up",
    questionId: "001313"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Slow down a bit! I can't keep up with you",
    answers: ["Slow down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Slow down",
    questionId: "001314"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that we would have to slow down the pace for a while",
    answers: ["slow down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "slow down",
    questionId: "001315"
  },
  {
    question:
        "All the goods were sold out",
    answers: ["sold out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "sold out",
    questionId: "001316"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I went away for an half hour",
    answers: ["went away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "went away",
    questionId: "001317"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Don't go away",
    answers: ["go away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "go away",
    questionId: "001318"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She couldn't hold back her tiers",
    answers: ["hold back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "hold back",
    questionId: "001319"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I can't understand what is holding you back ",
    answers: ["holding you back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "holding you back",
    questionId: "001320"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I haven't log in yet",
    answers: ["log in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "log in",
    questionId: "001321"
  },
  {
    question:
        "you need to log in first",
    answers: ["log in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "log in",
    questionId: "001322"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Don't forget to log out before switching off the computer",
    answers: ["logged out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "logged out",
    questionId: "001323"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I've already logged out of the system",
    answers: ["logged out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "logged out",
    questionId: "001324"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He often hangs out with his friends",
    answers: ["hang out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "hang out",
    questionId: "001325"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as I know he often hang out with his friends",
    answers: ["hang out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "hang out",
    questionId: "001326"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll have stay up late to finish everything",
    answers: ["stay up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "stay up",
    questionId: "001327"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As it seems to me I'll have stay up late tonight",
    answers: ["stay up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "stay up",
    questionId: "001328"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Looking back, I come to the conclusion that it was such a wise decision",
    answers: ["Looking back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Looking back",
    questionId: "001329"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Looking back, I realize that there was another reason for his refusal",
    answers: ["Looking back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Looking back",
    questionId: "001330"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll go out when the rain is over",
    answers: ["go out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "go out",
    questionId: "001331"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He put on the coat and went out",
    answers: ["put on/ went out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put on/ went out",
    questionId: "001332"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They're planning to carry out several experiments",
    answers: ["carry out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "carry out",
    questionId: "001333"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They said that they would carry out one more research",
    answers: ["carry out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "carry out",
    questionId: "001334"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that he wouldn't let us down",
    answers: ["let us down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "let us down",
    questionId: "001335"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It casts epproximately twenty dollars if my memory doesn't let me down",
    answers: ["let me down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "let me down",
    questionId: "001336"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It was decided to take on a new manager",
    answers: ["take on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "take on",
    questionId: "001337"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As they say the company should take on  more staff",
    answers: ["take on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "take on",
    questionId: "001338"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The chance that the price will go down if highly unlikely",
    answers: ["go down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "go down",
    questionId: "001339"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'm sure that this day will go down in history",
    answers: ["go down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "go down",
    questionId: "001340"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You need to think ahead before taking such important decision",
    answers: ["think ahead", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "think ahead",
    questionId: "001341"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Thinking ahead, i don't think that it's really worth it",
    answers: ["Thinking ahead", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Thinking ahead",
    questionId: "001342"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I came up against some serious obstacles while doing it",
    answers: ["came up against", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "came up against",
    questionId: "001343"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I came up against some serious difficulties while trying to do it ",
    answers: ["came up against", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "came up against",
    questionId: "001344"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He's to shy to ask her out",
    answers: ["ask her out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "ask her out",
    questionId: "001345"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Why don't you ask her out",
    answers: ["ask her out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "ask her out",
    questionId: "001346"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll try to get my idea across",
    answers: ["try to get", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "try to get",
    questionId: "001347"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll try to get my message across",
    answers: ["try to get", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "try to get",
    questionId: "001348"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I noted down her phone number",
    answers: ["noted down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "noted down",
    questionId: "001349"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You'd better note it down",
    answers: ["note it down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "note it down",
    questionId: "001350"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If I were you, I wouldn't dwell on these problems",
    answers: ["dwell on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "dwell on",
    questionId: "001351"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As you see, some mistakes were made but there is no need to dwell on it too much",
    answers: ["dwell on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "dwell on",
    questionId: "001352"
  },
  {
    question:
        "All the goods were bought up",
    answers: ["bought up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "bought up",
    questionId: "001353"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They bought up all the land in that area",
    answers: ["bought up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "bought up",
    questionId: "001354"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I won't be surprised if the price goes up",
    answers: ["goes up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "goes up",
    questionId: "001355"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The price went up by twenty percent ",
    answers: ["went up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "went up",
    questionId: "001356"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I haven't backed up these files yet but it's in my plans",
    answers: ["back up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "back up",
    questionId: "001357"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You'd better back up all these files just in case",
    answers: ["back up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "back up",
    questionId: "001358"
  },
  {
    question:
        "When will you be able to meet up",
    answers: ["meet up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "meet up",
    questionId: "001359"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I suppose that we could meet up the day after tomorrow",
    answers: ["meet up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "meet up",
    questionId: "001360"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He turned into a very successful businessman",
    answers: ["turned into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turned into",
    questionId: "001361"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It turned into a real nightmare",
    answers: ["turned into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "turned into",
    questionId: "001362"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It calls for more efforts",
    answers: ["calls for", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "calls for",
    questionId: "001363"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It calls for extra efforts",
    answers: ["calls for", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "calls for",
    questionId: "001364"
  },
  {
    question:
        "To their surprise, their plan fell through",
    answers: ["fell through", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "fell through",
    questionId: "001365"
  },
  {
    question:
        "In a word, their plan fell through completely",
    answers: ["fell through", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "fell through",
    questionId: "001366"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Yo need to warm up first before doing this exercises",
    answers: ["warm up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "warm up",
    questionId: "001367"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Let's do some exercises to warm up a bit",
    answers: ["warm up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "warm up",
    questionId: "001368"
  },
  {
    question:
        "This idea sounds quit good but we need to try it out ",
    answers: ["try out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "try out",
    questionId: "001369"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We could try out some of these ideas",
    answers: ["try out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "try out",
    questionId: "001370"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He was knocked out during the fight",
    answers: ["knocked out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "knocked out",
    questionId: "001371"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The boxer was knocked out in the second round",
    answers: ["knocked out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "knocked out",
    questionId: "001372"
  },
  {
    question:
        "As far as i Know they're going to bring down the price ",
    answers: ["bring down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "bring down",
    questionId: "001373"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They were asked to bring down the prices but it had no effect on them whatsever",
    answers: ["bring down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "bring down",
    questionId: "001374"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We were given out these sheets of paper before the exam",
    answers: ["given out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "given out",
    questionId: "001375"
  },
  {
    question:
        "When i saw him, he was giving out the leaflets",
    answers: ["giving out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "giving out",
    questionId: "001376"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We were handed out those materials",
    answers: ["handed out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "handed out",
    questionId: "001377"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The teacher handed us out these materials before the seminar",
    answers: ["handed out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "handed out",
    questionId: "001378"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She always shows off her knowledge and no one really likes it",
    answers: ["shows off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "shows off",
    questionId: "001379"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They just want to show off their wealth and abundance",
    answers: ["show off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "show off",
    questionId: "001380"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It's up to you",
    answers: ["is up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "is up",
    questionId: "001381"
  },
  {
    question:
        "This matter is up in the air",
    answers: ["is up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "is up",
    questionId: "001382"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Can I try it on",
    answers: ["try on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "try on",
    questionId: "001383"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She'd like to try on this dress",
    answers: ["try on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "try on",
    questionId: "001384"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If I were you, I would leap at this opportunity",
    answers: ["leap at", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "leap at",
    questionId: "001385"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If I were you, I would leap at this chance",
    answers: ["leap at", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "leap at",
    questionId: "001386"
  },
  {
    question:
        "So many companies went under during the crisis",
    answers: ["went under", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "went under",
    questionId: "001387"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It was reported that the company had gone under",
    answers: ["gone under", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "gone under",
    questionId: "001388"
  },
  {
    question:
        "How could we speed up the process?",
    answers: ["speed up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "speed up",
    questionId: "001389"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll try to speed up this matter",
    answers: ["speed up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "speed up",
    questionId: "001390"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I took up learning English recently",
    answers: ["took up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "took up",
    questionId: "001391"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He took up playing the guitar recently",
    answers: ["took up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "took up",
    questionId: "001392"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They put together this bookcase",
    answers: ["put together", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put together",
    questionId: "001393"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that he would put together his portfolio",
    answers: ["put together", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put together",
    questionId: "001394"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I go in for sports",
    answers: ["go in for", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "go in for",
    questionId: "001395"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I go in for swimming",
    answers: ["go in for", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "go in for",
    questionId: "001396"
  },
  {
    question:
        "What time will you check in?",
    answers: ["checked in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "checked in",
    questionId: "001397"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We've already checked in ",
    answers: ["checked in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "checked in",
    questionId: "001398"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Weight time will you check out?",
    answers: ["checked out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "checked out",
    questionId: "001399"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that they had already checked out",
    answers: ["checked out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "checked out",
    questionId: "001400"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Put on the jacket or you can get cold!",
    answers: ["put on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put on",
    questionId: "001401"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She said that she had put on some weight",
    answers: ["put on", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put on",
    questionId: "001402"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She said that she would heat up the soup",
    answers: ["heat up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "heat up",
    questionId: "001403"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that he would heat it up in a microwave",
    answers: ["heat it up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "heat it up",
    questionId: "001404"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Plug in the charger, please",
    answers: ["Plug in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Plug in",
    questionId: "001405"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The lamp isn't plugged in",
    answers: ["plugged in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "plugged in",
    questionId: "001406"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Let's get back to work!",
    answers: ["get back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get back",
    questionId: "001407"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Let's get back to previous point",
    answers: ["get back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "get back",
    questionId: "001408"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I take back my words",
    answers: ["take back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "take back",
    questionId: "001409"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I take back what i've just said",
    answers: ["take back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "take back",
    questionId: "001410"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He set off for work half an hour ago",
    answers: ["set off", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "set off",
    questionId: "001411"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I set off earlier because I didn't want to get stuck in a traffic jam",
    answers: ["stick to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "stick to",
    questionId: "001412"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I stick to the point that each of us must have equal opportunities",
    answers: ["stick to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "stick to",
    questionId: "001413"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I stick to the idea that our future is in our hands",
    answers: ["stick to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "stick to",
    questionId: "001414"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll be back",
    answers: ["be back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "be back",
    questionId: "001415"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He said that he wouldn't be back",
    answers: ["be back", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "be back",
    questionId: "001416"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It'll take him weeks to get over such series disease",
    answers: ["got over", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "got over",
    questionId: "001417"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Luckily, I got over all these difficulties on my way",
    answers: ["got over", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "got over",
    questionId: "001418"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The lesson is over",
    answers: ["is over", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "is over",
    questionId: "001419"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I don't really think that this crisis is over",
    answers: ["all over", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "all over",
    questionId: "001420"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It's all over",
    answers: ["all over", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "all over",
    questionId: "001421"
  },
  {
    question:
        "It's nessesary to look ahead before taking important decision",
    answers: ["look ahead", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look ahead",
    questionId: "001422"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Looking ahead, the current prices can increase by two or three times by the next decade",
    answers: ["Looking ahead", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "Looking ahead",
    questionId: "001423"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Look out ! It really dangerous",
    answers: ["look out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look out",
    questionId: "001424"
  },
  {
    question:
        "look out! There is a car coming",
    answers: ["look out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look out",
    questionId: "001425"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll look through these papers a bit later",
    answers: ["look through", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look through",
    questionId: "001426"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Let me look through this document",
    answers: ["look through", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look through",
    questionId: "001427"
  },
  {
    question:
        "What can we do about it?",
    answers: ["do about", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "do about",
    questionId: "001428"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I can do nothing about it",
    answers: ["do nothing about", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "do nothing about",
    questionId: "001429"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Unfortunately, there is nothing I can do about it",
    answers: ["do about", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "do about",
    questionId: "001430"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The thieves broke in and stole all jewellery",
    answers: ["broke in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "broke in",
    questionId: "001431"
  },
  {
    question:
        "The burglars broke in the window",
    answers: ["broke in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "broke in",
    questionId: "001432"
  },
  {
    question:
        "They split up after a year of marriage",
    answers: ["split up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "split up",
    questionId: "001433"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I was told that they had split up",
    answers: ["split up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "split up",
    questionId: "001434"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He was told to put away the toys",
    answers: ["put away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put away",
    questionId: "001435"
  },
  {
    question:
        "If you don't need it, you can out it away",
    answers: ["cut away", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "cut away",
    questionId: "001436"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I put it down to his laziness",
    answers: ["put it to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put it to",
    questionId: "001437"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I put it to her experience",
    answers: ["put it to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "put it to",
    questionId: "001438"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I come to the conclusion that it's mostly  a wast of time",
    answers: ["come to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "come to",
    questionId: "001439"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I come to the conclusion that it was done in vain",
    answers: ["come to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "come to",
    questionId: "001440"
  },
  {
    question:
        "When will his book come out ",
    answers: ["come through", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "come through",
    questionId: "001441"
  },
  {
    question:
        "This book has just come out",
    answers: ["come through", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "come through",
    questionId: "001442"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You can't imagine what i've come through",
    answers: ["come through", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "come through",
    questionId: "001443"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You can't imagine what i had come through",
    answers: ["come through", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "come through",
    questionId: "001444"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I look forward to hearing from you soon",
    answers: ["look forward to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look forward to",
    questionId: "001445"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I look forward to hearing from you in the near future",
    answers: ["look forward to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "look forward to",
    questionId: "001446"
  },
  {
    question:
        "She cut up the fish into small morsels",
    answers: ["cut up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "cut up",
    questionId: "001447"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He cut up the vegetables into small pieces",
    answers: ["cut up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "cut up",
    questionId: "001448"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I can't make out what she's talking about",
    answers: ["make out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "make out",
    questionId: "001449"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I can't make out what they're talking about",
    answers: ["make out", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "make out",
    questionId: "001450"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You don't need to dress up for dinner",
    answers: ["dress up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "dress up",
    questionId: "001451"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You don't have to dress up for this party",
    answers: ["dress up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "dress up",
    questionId: "001452"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He decided to dress up for that occasion",
    answers: ["dress up", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "dress up",
    questionId: "001453"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Some employees dress down on fridays",
    answers: ["dressed down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "dressed down",
    questionId: "001454"
  },
  {
    question:
        "He dressed down before a visit to his poor relatives because he didn't want to show off his wealth",
    answers: ["dressed down", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "dressed down",
    questionId: "001455"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I'll drop in on you if you don't mind",
    answers: ["drop in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "drop in",
    questionId: "001456"
  },
  {
    question:
        "Drop in at any time",
    answers: ["drop in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "drop in",
    questionId: "001457"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You can drop in at any time ",
    answers: ["drop in", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "drop in",
    questionId: "001458"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I bumped into him in a local shop",
    answers: ["bumped into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "bumped into",
    questionId: "001459"
  },
  {
    question:
        "I bumped him into on the way home",
    answers: ["bumped into", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "bumped into",
    questionId: "001460"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You need to wake up to the fact that their resources are rathe limited ",
    answers: ["wake up to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "wake up to",
    questionId: "001461"
  },
  {
    question:
        "You need to wake up to the situation",
    answers: ["wake up to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "wake up to",
    questionId: "001462"
  },
  {
    question:
        "We need to wake up to the fact that these resources aren't infinite",
    answers: ["wake up to", "Alan Sugar", "Donald Trump", "Bill Gates"],
    correct: "wake up to",
    questionId: "001463"
  }

];

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
